We've worked for a whole week straight...
Ririsa, is it... Done?
We still have to burn the DVDs, but...
Yeah, it's basically done!
I couldn't have done it without you!
You put in all the effort, Ririsa.
Time For Our First Event!
You're going to an event tomorrow?!
Wait, you were up all night with him too?!
How am I supposed to process all this?!
Would you like to go with me, Mikari-chan?
No way!
There's gonna be way too many people there!
You didn't do anything with him, did you?
Do what with who?
With Senpai!
Look, Ririsa, I hate that I have to ask this.
How do you feel about Senpai?
I'm going to the event with Ririsa.
In a way, it kinda feels like...
It kinda feels like a date!
No, I'm just helping a fellow club member!
That's right, this is a club event!
Like teammates going to a game!
Wait, what should I wear?
I don't have anything nice!
This isn't a date!
Calm down!
I bet Ririsa's not even thinking about her outfit!
Akiba
Moe everyday
As a person?
Yeah. How do you feel about him?
Well, we've got a lot in common...
He's helping me achieve my dreams,
and he's shy, but always so supportive...
This is gonna make me sound like an otaku,
but he's kind of like Ashford-sama!
Doesn't that basically mean you're into him?!
Huh?
Crap, I shouldn't have said that!
I'm into him?
Like, I have a crush on him?
That can't be right...
What should I wear tomorrow?!
I don't have anything nice!
Should I just go as Lilliel?
No, idiot!
Why am I so embarrassed about this?!
The event starts at 10,
but since it's our first time,
let's play it safe and take the earliest train!
I get playing it safe,
but we're way too early!
How are we gonna kill four hours?!
I don't look weird, right?
I wonder what Ririsa's gonna wear.
Probably something like this?
Lilliel
S-senpai!
Hey, Riri...
I hope you weren't waiting long.
I-is that really her?
Is this the "girl takes off her glasses" cliché?!
I-is my outfit weird? I don't look awful, do I?!
No, you look great, Ririsa!
I didn't know you were this fashionable...
I-I'm not, I just...
What should I wear to the event with Senpai?!
what clothes do otaku like
Virgin-killer
outfits
Should I buy one? No, idiot!
What?!
You want me to put together
an outfit for you?!
If I don't figure something out,
I'll end up buying the virgin-killer sweater!
The virgin-killer what?!
Where do you live?
That's not too far from me.
Ugh, fine.
Come over early tomorrow.
We'll show off your bust with a
boat neck and an off-the-shoulder top,
and put a tank top underneath for a bit of a sexy vibe.
You could go with palazzo pants,
but he'll like a miniskirt with a long belt better.
Oh, and a cross-body bag.
It's pretty hot for May so you can totally wear sandals,
with heels, of course.
And you HAVE to wear contacts.
I-if she says so...
There, that should do it.
Sorry for making you get up so early.
Yeah, this sucks.
But you made me a costume...
I put together an outift! We're even now!
But don't tell Senpai I helped you!
Thanks, Mikari-chan!
T-this was definitely too early to meet up...
I'm really sorry.
Hey, better to be too early than late.
We can go kill some time.
He sounds so calm.
I can't believe I was treating
this like it was a date...
What the hell?!
Ririsa's totally treating this like a date,
too, isn't she?!
No, calm down!
We're just two nerds going to a nerd event!
Still, we're here together, all dressed up...
We totally look like a couple!
Ririsa must be nervous for her first event.
I need to break the silence...
Wait! What are the go-to topics
for events in dating sims?!
We’ve got three hours...
What should we do?
You look cute today, Ririsa.
Nice weather today, huh?
What panties you wearing?
I-I'm glad it's nice out today!
The weather's always easy.
All she can do is agree. It's foolproof!
Yeah, it is.
But if it's too sunny,
our photos will come out way too bright.
It's actually better for it to be
cloudy for outdoor photoshoots.
Oh, come on!
I can do better than this!
I've gotta take charge here!
W-wanna go somewhere to hang for a bit?
S-sure, sounds good.
It's not open.
Crane Game
Special Campaign
First Play Free!
It's still really early.
There's a karaoke place nearby.
KARAOKE
And it just closed.
Ririsa looks upset.
This isn't good.
I've gotta turn things around!
MANGA CAFÉ
No rooms available.
Let's check out the other side of the station.
Maybe something's open over there.
Senpai?
Sorry, my feet really hurt...
You okay? Can I see?
I'm sorry.
I've never walked this much in heels before.
That's why she looked upset!
And I've been walking her all over the place...
Why didn't I notice?! I'm such a dumbass!
3D girls are way more complicated
than dating sim characters!
Dammit, I've ruined everything...
And now she's looking at her phone.
I can't say I blame her.
I've gotta say something...
Senpai...
Lilliel: Another World
Want to watch the spinoff episode?
I was busy getting ready so I missed it last night...
Huh?
Lilliel!
Ugh, this episode is epic!
I wish I could've seen it live!
God, me too!
I'm glad I got to watch it with you, though!
S-sorry.
Like, for not taking care of you, and now,
we're just watching anime on a bench...
Yeah...
But I always have fun with you.
I know we'll have a good time
no matter where we go.
She's right.
Honestly, I wouldn't mind a
3D girl if she was as cool as Ririsa...
No no, stop that, we're just club friends, that's all!
That's what Ririsa meant!
Right, Ririsa?
It's almost time for the event!
You're right!
Time flies when you're watching anime.
Is this it? It's kinda small.
I was expecting something massive like Comiket.
Photo Area
M-most cosplay-only events are like this!
T-this is actually one of the larger ones!
You okay?
I-I'm just nervous since it's my first time!
Let's see... Here's our booth.
Guess we'll set up our gear.
Actually, we... kinda don't have any.
I was so focused on finishing the ROM...
I totally forgot to print out covers or a poster!
Are people going to buy these?
Our neighbor is crazy.
Her ROMs look so pretty,
and look at that big poster!
Lady Folosso
Then look at us...
With our blank white DVD cases...
It looks so amateur.
Like, "look, we burned them all one by one!" Yikes.
At least I wrote the title on each DVD!
LILLIEL
500 PICTURES
That's worse!
Now it looks like some black market stuff!
Salutations, milady Magino!
Behold, your booth is fully assembled!
Hi, neighbors! I'm Magino.
Nice to meet you!
Wow! You're Lady Folosso!
I mean, nice to meet you, too!
H-hello.
Lady Folosso's from that huge mobile
game that just came out in March!
People are already cosplaying her?!
What are your names? And what are those?
I-it's our first time,
and we forgot a bunch of stuff...
Newbies, I see.
It's a Lilliel cosrom.
Lilliel?! That's so old!
Oh geez, sorry! I forgot the spinoff is still airing.
But you won't get a lot of attention unless
you're cosplaying current characters!
Or a lot of sales, if I do say so myself!
Don't be crass, Ogino.
Sorry, milady.
Hey, everyone's first time always sucks!
But cosroms are just business!
You can make it work if you're a good saleswoman!
Let's break a leg today!
Are you her photographer?
Huh? Uh, yeah...
You brought your costume, right?
If you dressed up, they'd know what these are,
and we might sell some!
I-I did...
But, I was gonna try selling
these without getting into costume...
What? Why?!
T-there are just so many amazing
cosplayers around us!
I-I'm worried I'm not as good as them.
I don't think I have the confidence.
I'm too nervous.
Y-you'll be fine!
Your Lilliel is so much cuter than-
I-I mean, it's really well-made!
She's really freaking out...
I guess I can't blame her.
But we have to do something...
Spring CosFest 19 is officially open!
Yeah, this tracks...
Ririsa is cute...
But she won't stand out in
a crowd of this many cosplayers.
Here are my new releases!
If you buy a whole set, you get a postcard, too!
I guess I'll get the whole set, then.
Thanks! Here's your set and the bonus postcard!
Lady Folosso
My, she's going to be your living,
breathing poster, then?
I'm sure you'll sell out in no time...
Oh, dear!
D-dammit!
If only they knew how cute she looked as Lillel!
C'mon, Lilliel!
You gotta tell everyone what you're selling!
Huh? You mean...
How are people gonna know what's inside
those blank cases if you don't tell them?
Hi, hello!
You mean talk to a stranger?
If it were that easy, I wouldn't be an otaku...
W-what is this? A cosrom?
A customer!
Are you the cosplayer? You're young.
Y-yes, I'm cosplaying Lilliel!
Lilliel?! What year is it?
Man, I dunno...
Wait... H-hold on.
Selling her cosrom means that other people
are gonna see her in all those poses...
I kinda don't like that.
Wait, what's wrong with me?
That's the whole thing she wanted!
Let me check how much I've got left. I'll be back.
Why am I so uncomfortable with that?
There he goes...
And now I'm relieved!
This isn't right.
I'm starting to hope we don't sell anything.
Why are you like this, Okumura?!
Are you in this cosrom?
Y-yes, I'm cosplaying Lilliel!
Are there panty shots?
No! None of them are sexy!
Senpai?
Crap! Why'd I say that?!
So, it's not an erotic photoshoot.
They're just normal photos, safe for work.
Oh, okay.
This is way too expensive, then.
Huh?
T-thanks anyways.
Ririsa, there really aren't any sexy pictures on these?
Huh?
Of course there aren't.
I can't sell anything softcore,
I'm under eighteen!
What?!
Then what'd we take all those sexy pictures for?
Those were all just for me!
Really?! Then...
I-I mean, I'm still a little too shy to let
other people look at those pictures.
Right now, I'm just happy
I have you as my photographer.
I had no idea.
I'm feeling relieved again.
Wait, am I jealous?!
Why am I acting like I'm her boyfriend?!
Senpai, let's just go home.
Huh?
We're not gonna sell anything.
I don't want to waste your precious time.
What's wrong with me?
How could I want her to fail?
My my... evacuating the premises already?
You must be popular to have sold out so quickly!
Think about how Ririsa might feel!
Y-you're really okay with ending things like this?
Huh?
Go get changed!
Let people see your Lilliel!
But...
I... I need to apologize to you.
Why?
For a moment, I hoped you wouldn't sell anything.
I didn't want someone other than
me seeing you dressed as Lilliel.
Wait, what's that supposed to mean?!
But that's not right!
Your dream was for everyone to
see your Lilliel cosplay, right?
That's why you asked me to help.
I said I'd never judge you!
This is your dream!
People need to see your Lilliel!
B-but why would they want me?
Everyone else is so much better than me.
What?!
Huh?
No, they're not!
Your Lilliel is the cutest in the entire world!
Wha?!
That day, our clubroom was graced by an angel!
Your Lilliel was so cute!
You made me, the world's biggest Lilliel fan,
think she was real!
You can do this!
Okumura-senpai...
C'mon, Ririsa!
Get into Lilliel, and show them you're the best!
Women's
Changing Room
When does the event end?
Um, we have to leave at 3:30.
Then we're almost out of time!
I-I'll change as fast as I can!
You'll show everyone you're the best Lilliel ever!
Yeah!
It usually takes her an hour to get into costume.
Hopefully she can make it in time...
Yay!
That's enough selfies.
H-hey...
T-that's the women's changing room!
Was that chick your girlfriend?
B-back off!
Sorry, sorry!
Don't worry. We're all girls here.
W-wait, you are? I'm so sorry!
Did you hear him? "Back off!" He's adorable.
C'mon, Akito!
You're sweet.
Every cosplayer needs a partner like you.
They're so handsome...
Little Brother
Guess I'll go wait in the photo area...
Okay, friends!
The line is getting long,
so please form a semicircle!
We'll take a break in sixty seconds!
Things are getting intense over there.
Nothing's doing it for me today.
It's all the usuals.
My, abandoning your cosplayer
to take some photos yourself?
Milady Magino is the number-one standout today,
so please, go right ahead!
Shut up! My Lilliel is number one!
Show ‘em, Ririsa!
Wanna get changed?
Has anyone seen my other sleeve?
Sorry, I've got it!
You wanna do the Vanga
concert outfits for the next event?
Yeah, I'll be Rei-tan!
It's so hot.
This outfit's dying on me.
Everyone's changing out of their costumes...
It's so crowded in here!
You can have my spot, I'm done!
Thank you!
Okay! I'm coming, Senpai!
Right, first, pull up my hair, put on my wig cap!
It's okay! Calm down and think.
Shoot, I forgot it!
I can't wear my wig without a wig cap!
Oh no, I'm missing a whole bunch of stuff...
It's ‘cause I was so distracted this morning...
I'm sorry, Senpai. I can't be Liliel today.
Do you need a wig cap?
Here you go.
Are you sure?! B-but aren't you leaving?
It's okay.
I always carry an extra just
in case someone needs one.
Huh?
Did you forget something?
What do you need?
I've got a spare binder, body tape,
safety pins, whatever you need!
What is happening right now?!
It's her first event!
You're gonna be Liliel! That takes me back!
You're showing a lot of underboob,
do you need pasties?
Or a stick-on bra?
All these anime characters want to help me!
Hurry, the event's almost over!
O-okay!
Wow, the stitchwork is so clean!
Where'd you buy it?
Oh, I made it.
You made that?!
For your first event? That's crazy!
Thank you for all this, but...
Are you sure you don't want everything back?
Don't worry about it!
Everyone's gotten stuff from
other cosplayers at least once.
That's why we always bring extra!
Make sure you return the favor to someone
in the future, okay, Liliel-chan?
I will!
Hold on...
Are you that girl from a while back?
Huh?
This is a softcore event,
so come back when you're in high school, mmkay?
You were with Mayura-sama!
Yeah, we're friends.
Wow. So glad you made it here.
Thanks.
Hurry, Lilliel!
The photo space is gonna close soon!
Okay!
Whoa, whoa, hold it!
You need something under that!
Huh?! But the panties are part of the costume!
Not when you're under eighteen!
Does anyone have a petticoat?
Definitely don't carry extras of those...
Emergency measures, then.
I'm leaving, so you can have mine.
Is that it?
You sure you've got everything?
Y-yes!
Thank you so much, everyone! I've gotta go!
Maybe I should go get pictures.
There's barely any time.
Me too.
I wanna get pictures with her.
I'm sorry...
Wait, why is Akito-sama in the girls' changing room?!
It's okay, I'm a girl. Talk about déjà vu.
Are you the girl who's with that guy outside?
He was pretty worried about you.
Senpai...
He was out there trying to keep you safe from me.
I can't blame him,
considering you're so cute.
You've got yourself a good partner out there.
Probably time for us to head out.
Yeah...
Oh, you're still here?
If that camera of yours is no toy,
why not take some of milady Magino?
Where's Lilliel-chan? Is everything okay?
Ririsa...!
Ashford-sama!
First Event Is Over!!